<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="pretty-atom-feed.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <title>Blog Title</title>
  <subtitle>This is a longer description about your blog.</subtitle>
  <link href="https://example.com/feed/feed.xml" rel="self" />
  <link href="https://example.com/" />
  <updated>2025-04-09T00:00:00Z</updated>
  <id>https://example.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name>Your Name</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <title>merchandise</title>
    <link href="https://example.com/blog/merch/merchandise/" />
    <updated>2025-04-09T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://example.com/blog/merch/merchandise/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;i&#39;ve been collecting otaku merchandise since 2020. (the year i got my own card, although it was one of those prepaid kinds for kids, controlled by parents...)
the very first figure i got was remilia scarlet from touhou project, for my birthday in october 2020..!!! i still love her a lot but komeijis reign supreme above all
other touhous i fear... here is a picture &lt;br&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://example.com/img/remilia.jpg&quot; width=&quot;300&quot;&gt;
i also have a decent collection of other anime figures as well... i&#39;ve been accumulating them slowly over the course of 5 years. i have had MUCH more in the past,
but ive either sold them or gave them to family members lmao... picture below&lt;br&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;https://example.com/img/merch1.png&quot; width=&quot;400&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
andddd let me show the merch wall... there are many many things on here and honestly not enough!!!!!!!!! if i had disposale income i would be spending it constantly....
&lt;img src=&quot;https://example.com/img/merch2.png&quot; width=&quot;400&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
i need more stuff of my goats (komeijis) and speaking of komeijis... i must show my ita bag of them because i love them so much (though i still feel like it could be improved)
&lt;img src=&quot;https://example.com/img/itabag.jpg&quot; width=&quot;300&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;
i am very very passionate about merchandise, and have even made some myself.. i made keychains of shimeji simulation characters (majime and shijima) and ayana otonashi. i really
want to make more keychains, but they cost a lot of money to manufacture... i get mine from vograce and theyre really nice quality, and for a understandable price ($50 for 20 ayanas, $42 for 12 shimejis..) but ouhhh i live in the united states and oggg the tariffs are gonna GET vograce shaking my head i hope orange guy lifts the china tariffs eventually because i need to make more keychains and other kinds of merch perhaps like stickers.... i may be really materialistic because of my passion for merchandise but whatever its my money&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>the surreal/unexplained</title>
    <link href="https://example.com/blog/unexplained/" />
    <updated>2025-04-05T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://example.com/blog/unexplained/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;since i was little, i have always liked media of an interpretive or open ended nature,
especially ones of the surreal genre..... in a previous (much more schloppity schlop) blogpost,
i had talked about something along the lines of this, so i will expand on that in a better way here. &lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;some examples of surreal media that fit this category are &lt;b&gt;angel&#39;s egg (1985)&lt;/b&gt; and &lt;b&gt;cat soup (2001)&lt;/b&gt;, two
of my favorite movies of all time. (my only favorite movies tbh... i dont really watch movies much) they are both
very very beautiful and of a surreal nature, something that fits my niche perfectly. for me, i really like stories where
the setting/plot is something unrealistic and out of this world in a peculiar or unique way. such as shimeji simulation, for another example... there is
great significance to me for stories where the author just lets their imagination run wild. i think that stories where its in way too realistic of a setting
are very boring.............. but this can depend of course..! i really like hidamari sketch even though there isnt really anything avant-garde about it...&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;avant-garde things, i really like in general. i like it when people create fiction or ideas that go out of the norm, even if it isnt always
appealing to me.... as of late, the mainstream media of today&#39;s society seems to be imploding on itself. big movie studios only want to make remakes of
their biggest hits for nostalgia bait, and when they DO make original stories again, they barely advertise them. and for books, it really seems like so many people
only want to consoom the schloppiest shit but maybe thats just booktok lmao, i dont use tiktok but i hear of stuff from it a lot... i try to buy books that appeal to me and are
classics and/or avant-garde, such as house of leaves and moby dick. i also read 1984 in school, for classics... getting back on topic, anime is victim of the sloppification as well.
why do so many anime studios greenlight manga titled like &amp;quot;I Got Transported To The Nether World And My Little Sister Is A Magical Demon God And She&#39;s In My Harem?!?!?&amp;quot; and not
stuff like shimeji simulation siiigh many people of today have no standards they just consoom whatever slop is put on their plate it seems.... i mean
to each their own i guess but i really wish studios didn&#39;t just greenlight whatever would make the most money... &lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;i really want to make my own thing with my vague ideas one day, but i doubt i have the mental strength to deal with a wide audience for it... i already cant handle stupid
people talking about my interests lol. maybe one day ill make my own cool surreal video game or other piece of art... though, sometimes it just Never gets far. one of my
favorite rpgmaker games of all time is ghost suburb 2, yet nobody ever really talks about it except for the nichest of circles. which is good but also annoying because theres little
discussion or fanart of it lol, please play it if you have a chance it&#39;s on gamejolt &lt;a href=&quot;https://gamejolt.com/games/ghost-suburb-ii-from-sleep-into-the-eyes-of-madness/20897&quot;&gt;here...!!!&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>new blog + stuff</title>
    <link href="https://example.com/blog/firstpost/" />
    <updated>2025-03-31T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://example.com/blog/firstpost/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;hello... i finally figured out how to use 11ty with the help of my very very awesome friend tm :pray:
it was tough to figure out how to do it at first, but got easier and easier... i really want to work on my site in
a more worthy way, like i currently feel like my site is just an art project/portfolio and not much else.. i want to
contribute good stuff to people..!!!!! an idea thats been floating around in my head for a while is having a recipes or food
creations page, i think that would be cool... one of my favorite blogs of all time is &lt;a href=&quot;https://touhousweets.tumblr.com&quot;&gt;touhousweets&lt;/a&gt;
on tumblr. i really want to make food themed after my favorite things like that, i think it would be really cool but i don&#39;t really have ideas often
and i&#39;m trying to lose weight anyways... :smiling_face_with_tear:&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;as of late i am pretty confident about the future, but with some things im not so confident about, like getting a job..... i really need to
save money for anime boston happening in two months!!! but i havent been able to get money lately due to a lack of commissions and workplaces getting back to me
about my applications... :graah: i hope i find a way to make more money soon... i really need to lock in but life is not handing me opportunities that much i fear&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;i also applied to a college this weekend. if i don&#39;t get in (slim chance of being rejected i think) idk what ill do since i dont really have alternatives that
i want to get into right now heeelpppp but i have high hopes...!!!! i really want to go to that college for a year or two and then transfer to a university in boston, for the
reason that i will get a much better opportunity to study what i actually want to...(which is linguistics and world history) among other reasons..... :happ:.....................
for this college in boston, the application window for first-year students closed months ago sadly, so i had to apply to a more nearby college. i&#39;ll get my credits in for the more local college, and then transfer...!!!!!!!!!!!! i must get a good job somewhere like the museum of fine arts in boston..&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <title>This is my third post.</title>
    <link href="https://example.com/blog/thirdpost/" />
    <updated>2018-08-24T00:00:00Z</updated>
    <id>https://example.com/blog/thirdpost/</id>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Leverage agile frameworks to provide a robust synopsis for high level overviews. Iterative approaches to corporate strategy foster collaborative thinking to further the overall value proposition. Organically grow the holistic world view of disruptive innovation via workplace diversity and empowerment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;code&quot;&gt;Code&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;this-is-a-very-long-heading-that-i-want-to-wrap-this-is-a-very-long-heading-that-i-want-to-wrap-this-is-a-very-long-heading-that-i-want-to-wrap-this-is-a-very-long-heading-that-i-want-to-wrap&quot;&gt;This is a very long heading that I want to wrap This is a very long heading that I want to wrap This is a very long heading that I want to wrap This is a very long heading that I want to wrap&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring to the table win-win survival strategies to ensure proactive domination. At the end of the day, going forward, a new normal that has evolved from generation X is on the runway heading towards a streamlined cloud solution. User generated content in real-time will have multiple touchpoints for offshoring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre class=&quot;language-js&quot; tabindex=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-js&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token comment&quot;&gt;// this is a command&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;function&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;token function&quot;&gt;myCommand&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;span class=&quot;token keyword&quot;&gt;let&lt;/span&gt; counter &lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;token number&quot;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
	counter&lt;span class=&quot;token operator&quot;&gt;++&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;span class=&quot;token comment&quot;&gt;// Test with a line break above this line.&lt;/span&gt;
console&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token function&quot;&gt;log&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token string&quot;&gt;&#39;Test&#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;token punctuation&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;heading-with-a-link&quot;&gt;Heading with a &lt;a href=&quot;https://example.com/blog/thirdpost/#code&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Bring to the table win-win survival strategies to ensure proactive domination. At the end of the day, going forward, a new normal that has evolved from generation X is on the runway heading towards a streamlined cloud solution. User generated content in real-time will have multiple touchpoints for offshoring.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;// this is a command
function myCommand() {
	let counter = 0;
	counter++;
}

// Test with a line break above this line.
console.log(&#39;Test&#39;);
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&quot;section-header&quot;&gt;Section Header&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Capitalize on low hanging fruit to identify a ballpark value added activity to beta test. Override the digital divide with additional clickthroughs from DevOps. Nanotechnology immersion along the information highway will close the loop on focusing solely on the bottom line.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
  </entry>
</feed>